Support for NPR Music comes from Capital
One, proud supporters of NPR Music and
the Tiny Desk Contest. What's in your
wallet? Learn more at capitalone.com.
>> [music]
>> I'm alone and lost [singing] on the
lonely highway,
paying for my sins.
The family sold me out last Friday
[singing] and lying [music] in me.
I'm getting used to getting sideways
till I can't see straight.
The angels know they don't
[music and singing] look my way. I'm way
too gone to say
I'm digging my grave down 12 feet deep.
I got none left, [singing] so I'm on my
knees, baby. Somebody say a prayer for
me cuz I'm all ran [music and singing]
out and I still can't sleep.
But somebody send a word upstairs cuz
the bar shut down and I've got no
[music] sway. I'm forced to knock on
heaven's door cuz my knee
>> [music]
>> ain't working [singing] anymore.
Somebody say a prayer for me. All I'm
asking for is a [music and singing]
little mercy. Amen.
>> [music]
[singing]
[music]
>> In a dusty silver auto
running [music] low [singing] on grace.
Going nowhere fast with my feet up on
the dash, just hoping I see the day
where I ain't ashamed of the [music] man
in [singing] the mirror. And the man
upstairs ain't either.
And I could finally set my life straight
and be the man my mama raised instead of
digging my grave down 12 feet deep. I
got none left, so I'm on my knees, baby.
Somebody say a prayer for [music] me cuz
I'm all ran and I still can't sleep.
Will somebody [music] send a word
upstairs cuz the bar shut down and I've
got no
where.
Won't you [music] knock on heaven's
door?
It's my only way in.
Will somebody say a prayer for me?
[music and singing] All I'm asking for
is a little mercy. Amen.
>> [music and singing]
[singing]
>> Will somebody [music] say a prayer for
me?
Amen. Will somebody [music] say a prayer
for me?
Will somebody say a prayer for me? Cuz
I'm all ran [music] out, and I still
can't sleep.
Will somebody send a word upstairs
[music] cuz the bar shut down and I've
got no
where.
Won't you [music] knock on heaven's
door?
It's my
only way
in.
Will somebody [singing] say a prayer for
me? All I'm asking for [music]
is a little mercy. Amen.
>> [singing]
[music]
[singing]
>> NPR, man.
>> [cheering and music]
>> Honestly.
Will somebody say [music] a prayer for
me?
>> [singing]
>> Amen. Will somebody say a prayer for me?
Will somebody say a prayer for me?
[music]
Amen. Will somebody say a prayer for me?
Hey,
will somebody say a prayer [music] for
me?
Hey,
will somebody say [singing] a prayer for
me? All I'm asking [music] for is a
little mercy. Amen.
>> [singing]
[music]
[singing]
[cheering and applause]
[applause]
[cheering]
>> Thank y'all so much.
>> [applause]
>> Can you keep it rocking?
Man.
And if you are, thank y'all so much. Um
I'm going to be playing some new songs
for y'all, some songs that uh
y'all never heard before, if you you
know. And I'm really excited. They're
from my new album, and uh I'm really
excited to be here, man, seriously. Um
>> [applause]
[cheering]
>> Uh
I can't tell you how nervous I was to do
this, but now being in front of all you
guys and feeling your energy, uh I'm so
calm and excited. So, thank y'all so
much. Thank you guys for being my my
comfort bear.
Y'all ready? Let's do it.
This song's called Drunk.
>> [music]
[music]
>> She sings to me so sweet and somber.
If she leaves my side oh tonight, I
wonder
what other lonely man shall comfort.
Please stay by [music] my side.
You're with me through the good and bad.
You're the best thing poor oh I've ever
had.
I'll cheers to you like [music] it's my
last. If I'm dying
tonight.
The
music to my western waltz,
the whole saloon will sit and watch
us dance [singing] about a
wooden room like angels
[music and singing] in the sky.
You damn near lost me everything. My cup
is empty as you can see.
There's nothing in here
left for me. If I'm dying, I want to die
drunk.
>> [music]
>> Your
lipstick and the taste are right.
I found my spirit [music] but damn near
lost my mind.
I killed a man, I'm going to jail
[singing and music] tonight.
But at least I'll
be drunk.
The
music to my
western waltz,
the whole saloon will
>> [music and singing]
>> sit and watch
us dance about this wooden room like
angels in the sky.
You damn near lost me everything.
My cup is empty
as you can see.
There's nothing in here [music]
left for me. If I'm dying
tonight.
>> [music]
>> If I'm dying.
If I'm dying, I want to die
drunk.
If I'm dying.
You're with me through the good and bad.
You're the best damn I've
ever had.
I'll cheers see you
like it's my last. If I'm dying, I don't
want to die drunk.
>> [applause and cheering]
>> I think some of you guys have been to my
shows, you know I like to talk, so
it's hard not to, but
man, I just wanted to say what a hell of
a year it's been, guys. So far, it's
just halfway through and it's already
felt like so much is going on and so
much is happening. I know a lot of
people out there need a little good
news, so let's give it to them. You all
ready?
Man, what a hell of a year it's been.
I keep on bluffing, but I just can't
win.
>> [music]
>> I drown my sorrows, but they learn to
swim.
Man, what a hell [singing] of a year
it's been.
My head [music] in a bottle, but my
heart in a cage.
Hell [music and singing] is getting
hotter than my
Play [music] this song on a tiny violin.
[singing]
For the man [music] at the bar
confessing his sins.
I need some good news. Send me some no
for truth. Nobody knows what I'm going
through. But the devil wouldn't walk in
my shoes.
If someone told me [music]
living this life would be lonely.
I'm trying to get away from the
lonely. [music]
Still stuck singing these blues.
All [music] I really need is a little
good news.
Love keeps knocking, but I just stay
home.
I ain't picking [music] no flowers in
this season of
>> [singing]
>> stone.
They say it gets darker when you're
coming home alone.
Still waiting for the ride at the end of
my road.
>> [music]
>> Oh, at the end [singing] of my road.
I need some good news.
>> [music]
>> Sitting here sipping on cold
truth.
Nobody knows what I'm going
>> [music and singing]
>> through.
Bet the devil wouldn't walk in my shoes.
I wish someone told
me,
>> [music]
>> living this life would be lonely.
I'm trying to get away from the lonely.
Still stuck [music] singing these blues.
All I really [music and singing] need is
a little good news.
>> NPR, man.
Thank y'all for bringing the good news
to the people. Come on.
Yeah.
I don't know if [music] y'all know how
many people need that.
I didn't know until I made this song.
Let's get some good news to people.
>> I need some good news. Sitting here
sipping [singing and music] on cold
truth. Nobody knows what I'm going
through. Bet the devil wouldn't walk in
my shoes.
I wish someone told
>> [music]
>> me,
living this life would be lonely.
I'm trying to get away [music] from the
lonely.
Still stuck singing these blues.
>> [music]
>> All I really [singing] need a little
good mood.
All I really need [music and singing] is
a little
something bring me back to the middle.
All I really [music and singing] need is
a little good
>> [music]
>> DMV right?
We in the DMV right? All my Virginia
people y'all got to know this one.
>> [music]
[music]
[cheering and applause]
[applause]
>> I just wanted to say this real quick man
DC literally you guys gave me my roots.
I played my first shows here ever when I
was 18 years old
and one thing about the DMV Virginia's
in the DMV too and we have
we have helped a lot carrying the DMV
music scene too. So you know, I just
wanted to play a little Roanoke for
y'all and and thank y'all for being here
man. Virginia's a part of the DMV and
we're really proud to to be here. This
is a very very important area
and I'm so proud to be here and let's
keep rocking out man. Seriously.
Also man shout out Sarah and Shawn
Watkins.
Come on. How y'all doing man?
>> Hey y'all, how y'all doing?
Yeah.
And um
I feel like uh it was important I
brought somebody out here with me.
Um this is a song off my new album, one
of my favorites I've ever written.
Uh
a legend
he's been here before, y'all may know
him.
Mr. Leon Bridges, LB5. [music]
>> [cheering]
[applause]
>> Hey, come on, [music] man.
Double trouble.
I told him earlier, I said, "Man, you
can't can't come on here come out here
dressing better than me, brother."
>> [music]
>> I heard it.
More than I do.
Let's get some revenge, baby.
>> [music]
>> I got something to tell them.
>> Come on.
>> Talk to them.
Girl, tell me who hurt you. Well, I'mma
do him way worse.
>> Ooh, what you got to do?
>> You buried all your secrets
under six feet of dirt.
>> I buried mine under six feet.
>> Even nature [music] just wants to
finish, girl, but get it straight, you
don't have to [singing] lie down.
It ain't [music] easy getting even,
[singing] if you need me, I can burn it
to the ground.
Hand on [music] your heart, [singing]
baby, tell me right now.
You would do it or not, [music]
all the pain you carry around.
I'mma catch a
if I ever find out.
I'mma take a match [music] to the sound.
[singing]
I'mma burn it down.
Burn it to the ground.
I'mma burn it all
>> [music]
>> down.
Burn it to the ground. [singing]
>> Like I said, man, this is a song about
revenge. That's all I can tell.
And I feel like when [music] you going
on a tour or going on a road down
revenge, you got to bring somebody with
you. You got to bring your getaway
driver.
We about to get our getback. Leon, get
your getback, baby. Get your getback.
>> [music]
>> Girl, I ain't perfect, but I never make
you hurt.
I can be a [music] solace, can be a
shotgun in the clutch. Baby, let me know
what you need, [singing] good or bad.
I would start [music] a riot for you,
babe.
>> Even angels [singing] won't forgive me.
I'mma turn the city upside down.
I'm no good at [music and singing]
getting even, but for you I'mma put the
call out.
You got your hand [music and singing] on
your heart, baby, tell me right now.
You've been through it all and your pain
you [music and singing] carry around.
I'mma catch a body if I ever find out.
I'mma [music] take a match to the sound.
I'mma burn it down.
Burn it to [music and singing] the
ground.
I'mma burn it all down.
Burn it to the ground.
>> Sarah D'ercole, everybody. Sarah
D'ercole [music] on mandolin from I'm
With Her.
Take it away, brother.
Like I said, we had to come get our
getback, right?
Man, what I said earlier that at the
rehearsal, I said, "Man, baby, you can
take [music] the low road." You know
what? Go even lower. Come on.
I mean, I know a lot of us want to get
revenge sometimes, man, and look, today
we ain't going to blame you. You get a
pass.
All right, let's do
Man, look.
Hand on your heart, baby, tell me right
now.
>> Tell me right now.
>> You've been through [singing] it all and
know the pain you carry around.
>> Know the pain you carry around.
>> I'mma catch you body if [music] I ever
find out.
I'mma take [singing] a match to this
town.
>> Hand on [music] your heart, baby, tell
me right [singing] now.
You've been through it all and know the
pain you carry around.
I'mma catch [music and singing] you body
if I ever find out.
I'mma take a match to this town. I'mma
burn it down.
>> [music]
>> Burn it to the ground.
>> [music and singing]
>> I'mma burn it all down.
>> [singing]
>> Burn it to the ground.
>> [cheering]
>> Leon Bridges, everybody. Leon Bridges,
man. Make some noise.
>> [applause]
>> MAN.
I'MMA NEED A LIGHT.
>> [applause]
>> IT'S HOT UP HERE, Y'ALL.
MAN.
MAN, thank you guys so much. Um
this is a fun experience, honestly. Uh I
didn't think it was going to be this
fun. I didn't I know I would know Well,
you know, you see on YouTube, it's just
in the corner of an office. I didn't
think it'd be this fun. But, um every
time anyone performs here, it's everyone
talks about how special the performances
are, and it's because of an environment
like this. Thank y'all so much.
Um
I got one more song for y'all. Hey,
kiddos. How y'all doing?
Okay. I got one more song for y'all.
Um it's not the song y'all expect.
>> [laughter]
>> Uh but, I got a new song coming I mean,
new album coming out. It's called The
Outlaw Cheryl Lee. It's a revenge
western. And um, there's a lot of cool
songs on it, one which you just heard.
So, you can tell it's going to be fire.
Come on.
Uh,
but I got another song for y'all, too.
So, you ready?
>> Yep.
>> Girl, shake it fast. Let me see you. Got
another bar song for you and all your
friends. Shooters got to shoot, [music]
so I got to take a chance. Girl, go and
throw your boots on. Thank me in
advance. Meet me on the dance [singing]
floor. Two-step to the left. Girl, you
found the right [music] one. Dolly said
it best. Treat her like a 9-5. We ain't
getting [singing] any. You can order
what you want. Girl, this tab don't ever
end.
We'll be at the [singing and music] bar
till 6:00 in the morning. Bomb paint
shots like some old logger.
Wild little cowgirl, [singing and music]
shoot them up, darling. Man,
I want to see you dance.
Baby got something in the back,
something serious. Shotgun in beer, she
don't [music] even know what fear is.
Man, let me see you hang. Wild little
[singing] cowgirl, I want to see you
dance.
Yeah,
god damn. I want to see you dance.
Go ahead [singing and music] back it up,
you wild little cowgirl. I want to see
you dance.
She's on the run.
I'm trying to catch her.
Baddest thing I ever seen, I had to ask
her, "Are you from Chattanooga,
Tennessee?"
Did you like this song? Let's put it on
repeat. Hit the dance floor. Two-step
[music] to the left. Girl, you found the
right one. Charlie said it best. We both
got a lot of pride. Why not put it to
the test? Bunch of stuff is in your
stepping, [music] but you know that we
the best. [singing]
We'll be at the bar till 6:00 in the
morning. Bomb paint shots like some old
logger.
Wild [music] little cowgirl, shoot them
up, darling. [singing] man, I want to
see you dance.
Baby got something in the back, some
serious shotgun and beer. She don't
[music] even know [singing] whose beer
it is, man. Let me see your hands. Wild
little cowgirl, I want
[music and singing] to see you dance.
God damn, I want to see you dance.
Go ahead,
>> [music]
>> back it up. You're a wild little
cowgirl. I want to see you dance.
If you're a wild gosh.
Y'all turned this into a dive bar. I
love y'all so much.
Come on, man. I can't wait for this song
to come out. Y'all have been [music]
amazing. Y'all have been one heck of a
crowd. You know what I mean? I think we
should turn it up one more time, right?
Come on, man.
Let's turn this into a party one more
time. Let's turn it into a party, y'all
ready? All right.
We be at the bar till 6:00 in the
morning, going beige shots like some
cold liquor.
Wild little cowgirl, shoot them up,
darling man, I want to see you dance.
Baby got something [music] in the back,
some serious shotgun and beer. She don't
even know whose beer it is, man. Let me
see your hands. Wild little cowgirl,
[singing and music]
I want to see you dance.
>> [music]
>> I want to see you dance.
Go ahead, back it [singing] up. You're a
wild little cowgirl. I want to see you
dance. [music]
>> [cheering]
>> Let y'all see something.
>> [applause]
>> Thank y'all.
>> [cheering]
[cheering]
>> Oh, god damn.
>> [applause]
>> Jesus.
Uh.
>> [cheering]
>> Gosh.
>> [applause]
>> Man.
>> Thanks for watching. Support for NPR
Music comes from Rivian, makers of
all-electric adventure vehicles designed
with the planet and future generations
in mind.
A quick update before you go. We're
doing another Tiny Desk giveaway. Enter
by September 12th, 2026 and you and a
friend could win a free trip to DC to
see a Tiny Desk Concert live in person.
You even get to choose which upcoming
show you want to see and it's completely
free to enter. Just go to
npr.org/tinydeskgiveaway.
Entering is completely free, but you can
get more entries by snagging some
limited edition Tiny Desk merch or by
making a special donation to the NPR
network. Learn more and enter today at
npr.org/tinydeskgiveaway.